<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Alex on hughsambros.</title>
    <link>https://www.hughsambros.com/categories/alex/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Alex on hughsambros.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2018 17:31:13 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.hughsambros.com/categories/alex/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>AKC#1: I AM NOW AN NHL ALL-STAR!!</title>
      <link>https://www.hughsambros.com/blog/2018/02/akc1-2-i-am-nhl-allstar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2018 17:31:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hughsambros.com/blog/2018/02/akc1-2-i-am-nhl-allstar/</guid>
      <description>Hey everyone! Yup, I&amp;rsquo;ve been pretty bad with updating the blog, BUT unlike the vision board, I was able to complete the challenge (GO ME)!!
Since I haven&amp;rsquo;t uploaded a lot, here&amp;rsquo;s me ALMOST completing the challenge the day before:   And here&amp;rsquo;s a video of me completing the challenge the morning after with a few kids in the background watching me do it (can only hear them not see them):   What I did well:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AKC#1: Hockey Update</title>
      <link>https://www.hughsambros.com/blog/2018/01/akc1-1-hockey-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2018 10:49:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hughsambros.com/blog/2018/01/akc1-1-hockey-update/</guid>
      <description>This challenge has been a lot harder than what I thought, and not for the reasons that I thought either! Let me explain. For one, it&amp;rsquo;s fairly hard to find a right time to go out and practice on ice, because it has to be perfect conditions.
It can&amp;rsquo;t be rainy, it can&amp;rsquo;t be snowy (if not you can easily lose your pucks, you have to shovel a lot and you have less space to actually play) and it can&amp;rsquo;t be freezing outside (by freezing, I mean lower than -30 oC).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AKC#1: the Hockey Challenge</title>
      <link>https://www.hughsambros.com/blog/2018/01/akc1-0-the-hockey-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2018 11:33:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hughsambros.com/blog/2018/01/akc1-0-the-hockey-challenge/</guid>
      <description>My first challenge of 2018 is the hockey challenge!
Background:
My love for hockey has been back and forth while growing up. I&amp;rsquo;ve only played casual hockey when I was younger, and only recently have I decided to join a league (a ball hockey league, since I JUST decided to learn how to skate). So I am not starting from scratch, but I am very far away from being a &amp;lsquo;good&amp;rsquo; hockey player.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AKC#0: First Challenge... Failed</title>
      <link>https://www.hughsambros.com/blog/2018/01/akc0-first-challenge-failed/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2018 14:49:23 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hughsambros.com/blog/2018/01/akc0-first-challenge-failed/</guid>
      <description>Yup. I failed. The first challenge of this project and I am starting with a failure. Certainly, not the way I wanted my 2017 to end, but it is what it is. Instead of sulking and making excuses for why I didn&amp;rsquo;t complete this challenge, I thought it would be a lot more instructional for me to list what were my mistakes and what I could&amp;rsquo;ve done instead to turn this failure into a learning experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AKC#0: Yup... I&#39;m Fucked</title>
      <link>https://www.hughsambros.com/blog/2017/12/akc0-yup-im-fucked/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2017 12:42:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hughsambros.com/blog/2017/12/akc0-yup-im-fucked/</guid>
      <description>Alright, so it&amp;rsquo;s December 29th and I still haven&amp;rsquo;t started my vision board. What&amp;rsquo;s worst, is that I have something planned every day until the New Year, so I have even less (no) time to complete my challenge! BUT NO EXCUSES! I am going to start the New Years on a good note and complete this vision board. At the very least, I already bought a cork board and some pins as well, so that&amp;rsquo;s a start.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AKC#0: Create a Vision Board</title>
      <link>https://www.hughsambros.com/blog/2017/12/akc0-create-a-vision-board/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 12:34:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hughsambros.com/blog/2017/12/akc0-create-a-vision-board/</guid>
      <description>My first challenge is to create my own vision board.
Background:
Around a year ago, I decided to get a life coach, because I was really interested in self development, and since I had some extra cash lying around, I decided to use that to good use and invest it on myself. After a few sessions with her, one of my tasks was to create a vision board. To be completely honest, I did a really botched job of creating one, and didn&amp;rsquo;t even look at it or use it after the fact.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KC: Introducing the Kaizen Challenge</title>
      <link>https://www.hughsambros.com/blog/2017/12/kc-introducing-the-kaizen-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2017 11:58:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hughsambros.com/blog/2017/12/kc-introducing-the-kaizen-challenge/</guid>
      <description>The whole idea of starting hughsambros.com came after I read through Max Deutsch&amp;rsquo;s project he called Month to Master (M2M). During this project, Max spent one year trying to complete 12 super hard challenges (tackling 1 every month) such as drawing a realistic self-portrait, solving a Rubik&amp;rsquo;s cube in 20 seconds, memorizing the order of a deck of cards in less two minutes and doing a freestyle-rap for 3 min.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>