<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rap on hughsambros.</title>
    <link>https://www.hughsambros.com/tags/rap/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Rap on hughsambros.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 22:21:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.hughsambros.com/tags/rap/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>NKC#2: Rap Update</title>
      <link>https://www.hughsambros.com/blog/2018/02/nkc-2-rap-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 22:21:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hughsambros.com/blog/2018/02/nkc-2-rap-update/</guid>
      <description>Hey yaaaaalll !!!
I know it&amp;rsquo;s been a really long time that we haven&amp;rsquo;t posted, but we were pretty busy with our lives. However, especially for our rap challenge, I think it&amp;rsquo;ll be a good idea if you follow us on Youtube or on our Instagram if you want more rap updates.
I&amp;rsquo;m just going to make a short post here, but freestyling is actually really fun to do and there were lots of trial and error at the beginning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NKC#2: Introducing the Rap Challenge</title>
      <link>https://www.hughsambros.com/blog/2018/02/nkc2-1-rap-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 11:10:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hughsambros.com/blog/2018/02/nkc2-1-rap-challenge/</guid>
      <description>My second challenge of 2018 is the rap freestyle challenge!
Background: Imagine the scene where you&amp;rsquo;re at a metro station or a public space and someone starts playing an instrumental song. The beat is real nice, but you won&amp;rsquo;t listen to it more than 3 minutes because it gets repetitive. Suddenly, a dude comes out of nowhere, grabs a mic and starts rapping off his head aka freestyling. Then, people start filming, people post on youtube, shit gets 20M views, the dude goes on Ellen and the rest is history.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AKC#2: Introducing the Rap Challenge</title>
      <link>https://www.hughsambros.com/blog/2018/02/akc2-1-rap-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 22:58:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hughsambros.com/blog/2018/02/akc2-1-rap-challenge/</guid>
      <description>My second challenge of 2018 is the rap freestyle challenge!
Background:
If you&amp;rsquo;ve known me for a while, then you probably know that I love hip-hop and rap (extra props if you know who my favourite rapper is). To be completely honest, I&amp;rsquo;ve always put more importance to the beat and the vibe of the song, more so than the actual lyrics (yup just lost all my street cred), but I still love going on RapGenius to look up the meaning of the lyrics of each song I listen to.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>