<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nich on hughsambros.</title>
    <link>https://www.hughsambros.com/categories/nich/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Nich on hughsambros.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 15:03:09 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.hughsambros.com/categories/nich/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>NKC#1: Gordon Ramsay, Where You At?!</title>
      <link>https://www.hughsambros.com/blog/2018/02/nkc1-4-my-final-meals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 15:03:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hughsambros.com/blog/2018/02/nkc1-4-my-final-meals/</guid>
      <description>Hey !! This is a recap post about my challenges, as a bonus I even put an extra meal that I did (my own recipe, waddup Gordon).
I don&amp;rsquo;t really know how to organize this post so I&amp;rsquo;ll just write the same format as Alex and then randomly insert pictures of my final results.
All in all, I would give myself a pass, but I only passed the taste test and failed every other criteria that I set myself so&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;m the only one that can be blamed for that&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NKC#1: Two Steps Forward, One Step Back. The Pasta Story</title>
      <link>https://www.hughsambros.com/blog/2018/01/nkc1-3-my-third-meal/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2018 22:17:07 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hughsambros.com/blog/2018/01/nkc1-3-my-third-meal/</guid>
      <description>It was a Wednesday night I think (I actually don&amp;rsquo;t know, it just sounds cool to have a specific day) and I was casually scrolling on Facebook, doing my relaxing-brainless activity of the day when I stumbled across a video of a couple doing cooking show called &amp;lsquo;Night In/ Night out&amp;rsquo;. It&amp;rsquo;s a pretty cool concept, where this average couple compares the worth of having a night in vs a night out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NKC#1: My Second Meal</title>
      <link>https://www.hughsambros.com/blog/2018/01/nkc1-2-my-second-meal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2018 10:42:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hughsambros.com/blog/2018/01/nkc1-2-my-second-meal/</guid>
      <description>I LOVE SOUTH AMERICAN FOOD. And I&amp;rsquo;m not talking about the actual taste because I don&amp;rsquo;t think I ever ate any authentic South American food; I&amp;rsquo;m talking about the idea of rice, beans, meat, avocado, salsa, tomatoes, onions and plantains all packed together into a single dirt cheap, but utterly delicious meal ! Now, I know, those probably aren&amp;rsquo;t the most healthy meals, but hey, can&amp;rsquo;t a man just enjoy his good food in peace?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NKC#1: My First Meal</title>
      <link>https://www.hughsambros.com/blog/2018/01/nkc1-1-my-first-meal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 15:03:56 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hughsambros.com/blog/2018/01/nkc1-1-my-first-meal/</guid>
      <description>Ever since I can remember, Wednesdays have always been pasta day in our house. I always found it really peculiar that we had a pasta day in an asian household. I mean, think about it, how many asian families do you know that doesn&amp;rsquo;t eat white rice everyday and even worse, that eats pasta EVERY Wednesday? I, personally, don&amp;rsquo;t know any other asian household, but I guess it has to do less with the fact that we&amp;rsquo;re asian and more with the fact that my mom absolutely LOVES Italian cooking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NKC#1: the Cooking Challenge</title>
      <link>https://www.hughsambros.com/blog/2018/01/nkc1-0-the-cooking-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2018 13:52:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hughsambros.com/blog/2018/01/nkc1-0-the-cooking-challenge/</guid>
      <description>My second challenge is to be able to cook by the end of January 2018.
Why I&amp;rsquo;m Doing a Cooking Challenge:
I simply don&amp;rsquo;t know how to cook. Okay yes, I can cook instant ramen, make eggs in the morning, put a toast in the toaster and spread some butter or peanut butter on it, but I don&amp;rsquo;t ACTUALLY know how to cook anything else. It&amp;rsquo;s a bit sad to say, but at 22 years old, if my mom would leave us at home for 2 weeks straight, we would probably gain 5lbs each from always eating out or die (one of the two, no in-betweens really).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NKC#0: Im Done !!... Kinda</title>
      <link>https://www.hughsambros.com/blog/2018/01/nkc0-im-done-kinda/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 14:40:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hughsambros.com/blog/2018/01/nkc0-im-done-kinda/</guid>
      <description>As you can see, the site is still the same and that is because I have FAILED my first challenge&amp;hellip;. I really wanted to go LIVE with the real website before 2018, but I guess that 6 days isn&amp;rsquo;t enough to learn how to build and DEPLOY a website. However, the good news is that I managed to complete it today and I really like the results. Right now, the only thing left to do is to connect it to Netlify CMS, which is a content management software tool that will allow Alex and I to write our posts online instead of having to write &amp;ldquo;code&amp;rdquo; aka directly in the file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NKC#0: Whats a Static Website</title>
      <link>https://www.hughsambros.com/blog/2017/12/nkc0-whats-a-static-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 12:38:53 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hughsambros.com/blog/2017/12/nkc0-whats-a-static-website/</guid>
      <description>HEY GUYS !!! I&amp;rsquo;m finally DONE with school and am totally ready to start building the new website (yayyy, I only have like 4 days left to build it), but before I do, I just want to write a brief post about what exactly is a static website.
If you take all the websites that exist, you can separate them into 2 broad categories. The first one is Dynamic Websites and the second one is Static Websites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NKC#0: Build A Static Website</title>
      <link>https://www.hughsambros.com/blog/2017/12/nkc0-build-a-static-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2017 12:23:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hughsambros.com/blog/2017/12/nkc0-build-a-static-website/</guid>
      <description>My first challenge is to build a static website that will replace the current website in 2018.
Background:
I&amp;rsquo;ve always had an interest in building a static website, but I never found any good motivation to do it so when HughSamBros came up, I jumped at the gun and told Alex that I&amp;rsquo;ll take care of the website. The initial plan was to start right off the bat with the static website and document everything on it; however, I wanted the site to be my first challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>